NAME:
   redpanda-connect - A stream processor for mundane tasks - https://docs.redpanda.com/redpanda-connect

USAGE:
   redpanda-connect [global options] command [command options]

DESCRIPTION:
   Either run Redpanda Connect as a stream processor or choose a command:

     redpanda-connect list inputs
     redpanda-connect create kafka//file > ./config.yaml
     redpanda-connect run ./config.yaml
     redpanda-connect run -r "./production/*.yaml" ./config.yaml

COMMANDS:
   dry-run     Parse Redpanda Connect configs and test the connections of each plugin
   agent       Redpanda Connect commands.
   mcp-server  Execute an MCP server against a suite of Redpanda Connect resources.
   plugin      Plugin management commands
   echo        Parse a config file and echo back a normalised version
   lint        Parse Redpanda Connect configs and report any linting errors
   run         Run Redpanda Connect in normal mode against a specified config file
   streams     Run Redpanda Connect in streams mode
   list        List all Redpanda Connect component types
   create      Create a new Redpanda Connect config
   test        Execute Redpanda Connect unit tests
   template    Interact and generate Redpanda Connect templates
   blobl       Execute a Redpanda Connect mapping on documents consumed via stdin or file
   help, h     Shows a list of commands or help for one command

GLOBAL OPTIONS:
   --version, -v                                              display version info, then exit (default: false)
   --secrets env: [ --secrets env: ]                          Attempt to load secrets from a provided URN. If more than one entry is specified they will be attempted in order until a value is found. Environment variable lookups are specified with the URN env:, which by default is the only entry. In order to disable all secret lookups specify a single entry of `none:`. (default: "env:")
   --redpanda-license /etc/redpanda/redpanda.license          Provide an explicit Redpanda License, which enables enterprise functionality. By default licenses found at the path /etc/redpanda/redpanda.license are applied.
   --chroot value                                             Chroot into the provided directory after parsing configuration. Common /etc/ files are copied to the chroot directory, and the directory is made read-only. This flag is only supported on Linux.
   --chroot-passthrough value [ --chroot-passthrough value ]  Specify additional files to be copied into the chroot directory. This flag can be used multiple times. It is only supported when --chroot is used.
   --disable-telemetry                                        Disable anonymous telemetry from being emitted by this Connect instance. (default: false)
   --rpc-plugins value [ --rpc-plugins value ]                Plugins to load over the RPC interface. This flag should point to manifest files containing the plugin definitions. Globs are also supported.
   --help, -h                                                 show help
